voyage.tv 2011-11-02

# Privacy Policy - Voyage.tv

**Privacy Policy**

Voyages North America Inc. (“we,” “us,” “our,” “Voyage.tv” or “Voyages”) operates voyage.tv (the “Website”).  We respect your ability to make informed choices about the collection and uses of your personal information.  This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) is designed to tell you about the collection and uses of information from this Website so that you can make an informed choice about using this Website.  The terms in this Privacy Policy apply to the information we collect about our Website users, unless different terms are specified on-line or in other form or contract provided to you by us or by one of our subsidiaries, affiliates or third party associates.

 ** _Information We Collect and How We Use It_**

When you visit this Website, some information such as the website that referred you here, your IP address, and your electronic mail address may be automatically collected as part of the operation of our Website.  We use this information to generate user profiles and to personalize our Website to your particular interests.  We may share statistical information about users of our Website with our third party associates.

Sometimes we may require you to provide certain information on our Website.  For example, we may require you to register for an account, we require you to provide information such as your user name, password, full name, telephone number, electronic mail address and mailing address. We collect your name, telephone number, electronic mail and mailing address so that we can process your orders efficiently, and contact you if we encounter some difficulty. We also may require you to provide information, including your credit card number, or other personally identifying information, in order to fulfill licensing transactions or provide service to you as a customer. In addition, we occasionally may ask you to provide other categories of information, such as your age, hobbies, income, gender, and the like so that we may customize and personalize the Website for your specific interests. When information is optional, it will be marked as such. 

The personal information collected from this Website is stored indefinitely and may be disclosed to our various worldwide offices, subsidiaries, affiliates, and any necessary payment processors. The personal information we collect is used for various purposes, such as processing your transactions, customer service, marketing, product and service development, facilitating your use of this Website, customizing your image selection and personalizing the Website to your interests ** _.   _**Because of the nature of the Internet, such data may pass through any country.

Unless you opt out of receiving promotional materials, we may send you information by electronic mail or regular mail to the address you provide on the registration. From time to time we may notify you of special promotions, new products or services, or other information that may interest you.  You may also receive notifications of special promotions, new products or services from our third party associates.  You also should be aware that we reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or protect the rights, property or safety of our company, employees, customers, or the public.

 ** _Information Security_**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.  We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. Credit card data and passwords are stored in encrypted format for increased security.  Our servers are protected by firewalls and are physically located in secure data facilities to further increase security.  While no computer is 100% safe from outside attacks, we believe that the steps we have taken to protect your personal information dramatically reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

 ** _About Cookies_**

When you visit the Website, we place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser directory of your computer’s hard drive.  A cookie is a small piece of information that a website can store on your web browser and later retrieve.  The information we collect by use of cookies includes the dates and times you visit, your registration information, and your navigational and purchase activity on our Website.  Cookies offer you many conveniences.  For example, they enable this Website to recognize the information you have created, and help us determine what services, products, and portions of this Website are most appropriate for your needs.  Cookies also allow you to retrieve previous search results, access appropriate pages with ease, and view your previous orders and invoices.

We do not and cannot use cookies to retrieve individual personally identifying information about you from your computer unless you knowingly and willingly provided such information.  The cookie technology we use cannot obtain information from your hard drive or pass on a computer virus.  You can adjust your web browser security settings to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you disable the use of cookies in your web browser, some features or services we offer on the Website may not function properly.

 ** _Opting Out_**

If you do not want to receive promotional information from us, our affiliates, subsidiaries or our third party associates, you will be able to express this preference by clicking on the appropriate button or checkbox provided on the screen on which you fill out on-line forms. 

If you do not want to receive promotional material from us or our third party associates and you did not indicate this preference when you initially registered with us, you may contact us at [optout@voyage.tv](mailto:optout@voyage.tv?subject=Opting%20Out%20of%20Voyage.tv%20Mailings) to change your preferences.  We will take reasonable steps to deactivate your name from our marketing ** __** lists when we receive your request.  We will not be responsible, however, for recalling information we previously provided to our third party associates prior to receiving and processing your opt out request.

 ** _Reviewing, Updating, or Correcting Your Information_**

If you would like to review or revise the personal information you previously provided to us, or believe that what we currently have on record is incorrect, you may update the information in the account section of this Website found at http://www.voyage.tv/Pages/signin.aspx

 ** _Links to Other Websites_**

Our Website may contain links to other websites.  We do not control these websites and we are not responsible for their uses of personal information, or for any harm or loss suffered by you in relation to the use of these websites.  You should familiarize yourself with the privacy practices of any linked websites when you visit them. 

**_Children_**

This Website is not intended for children. Children may only use this Website with direct supervision of a parent or legal guardian. We do not knowingly request or collect personal identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13 years old nor do we knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years old with third parties.

 ** _Sale of Assets_**

If another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets related to our business, we reserve the right to include any or all stored personal information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company.

 ** _Questions or Concern_** _s_

If at any time you believe that we have not followed this Privacy Policy, please let us know by sending an email to [privacy@voyage.tv](mailto:privacy@voyage.tv?subject=Opting%20Out%20of%20Voyage.tv%20Mailings). We will use reasonable efforts to identify and correct any problem.

 ** _Changes to This Privacy Policy_**

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time.  If we do change this Privacy Policy, we will post changes on this Website.  We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy when you visit our Website so you understand how we use information we collect.
